Guide to the Atlantic Philanthropies Archives, 1982-2017.
Atlantic Philanthropies Archives,
- Series IV: Grant Files
  - Subseries F: Northern Ireland grant files, 1977-2018
    - Integrated Education Fund, 1992, 1994-2014
      - Volunteer handbook, 2007 (Box 124, Folder 3)
      - Reports, plans, and general information, 2008 (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - #7416 (#96-41) Consultancy advice; #7577 (#97-104); #7754 (#98-124). Fundraising campaign. File 2, 1998-1999 (Box 124, Folder 5)
        File number N 13/2/1
      - #7577 (#97-104). Fundraising campaign. File 1, 1992, 1994-1998 (Box 124, Folder 6-7)
        File number N 13/2/1/1
      - #7668 (#98-35). All Ability Teaching Program. Oakgrove Integrated School, 1997-2000 (Box 124, Folder 8-9)
        File number N 13/3.
      - #7668 (#98-35). Oakgrove Integrated College supplemental materials, 1996-1997, 2002 (Box 124, Folder 10)
        File number N 13/3
      - #7977 (#00-1). Core support. Ulidia., 1992, 1994, 1999-2000 (Box 124, Folder 11)
        File number N 13/8
      - #8009 (#00-32) and #10118. Development program, 2000, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 9)
        Folder previously processed by the Winthrop Group
      - #8009 (#00-32). Development fund. File 3, 1994, 1999-2001 (Box 124, Folder 12-13)
      - #8009 (#00-32). Development fund. File 4, 2001-2003 (Box 124, Folder 14-15)
      - #8009 (#00-32). Development fund. File 5, 1996-2004 (Box 124, Folder 16)
      - #10118. Development program support- extension, 2001-2003 (Box 125, Folder 1)
        File number N 13/2/1/4
      - #10118. Development program support- extension. Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 125, Folder 2)
        File number N 13/2/4
      - #12255. Core revenue support, 2003-2004 (Box 125, Folder 3)
        File number N 13/2/1/5
      - #12255. Core revenue support, 2003 (Box 168, Folder 10)
        Dublin office cabinet file Cab. 6, Dr. 3A 17/7/3/6.
      - #13573. Growth of integrated education, 2004-2008 (Box 125, Folder 4)
      - #13573. Growth of integrated education. File 1, 2004-2007 (Box 125, Folder 5-6)
        File number N 28/7/4
      - #13573. Growth of integrated education. File 1, Feb. 16th - Nov. 30th, 1992, 2004-2005 (Box 125, Folder 7)
      - #13573. Growth of integrated education. File 2, 2006-2007 (Box 125, Folder 8)
      - #13573. Growth of integrated education. File 3, 2007-2008 (Box 125, Folder 9-11)
        File number N 28/7/4.
      - #17541. Growing capacity and strengthening advocacy, 2009 (Box 125, Folder 12)
      - #17541. Growing capacity and strengthening advocacy. Core support, 2001, 2009-2012 (Box 125, Folder 13-16)
        File number N 28/7/48
      - #18592. Supporting integrated education through transformation, 2010-2014 (Box 126, Folder 1-2)
        File number N 28/7/55
    - Interactive Aging Network, 2002, 2004-2006
      Interactive Aging Network
      - David Dring/Benefits Take-Up, 2004-2005 (Box 126, Folder 3-4)
        File number N 26/8/18. No grant-related documents.
        Dring, David
      - Supplemental materials, 2002, 2005-2006 (Box 126, Folder 5)
      - #13601. Joint Benefits Take-Up Initiative, 2005-2006 (Box 126, Folder 6)
      - #13601. Joint Benefits Take-Up Initiative, 2004-2006 (Box 126, Folder 7-8)
        File number N 26/8/14
    - Intercomm, 2000-2013; Intercomm (Organization)
      Intercomm (Organization)
      - Area based planning - Area 3 - North Belfast, 2007-2008 (Box 126, Folder 9)
        File number N 28/7/29. Materials refer to building peace within communities in Belfast and Northern Ireland. No grant-related documents.
      - #8516. Intercomm leadership, 2000-2003, 2006 (Box 126, Folder 10)
        File number N 17/43
      - #11059. North Belfast Conflict Intervention Program, 2002-2007 (Box 126, Folder 11-12)
        File number N 17/51
      - #17582. Investing in an implementation framework to deliver a shared future, 2009-08 (Box 126, Folder 13)
      - #17582. Investing in an implementation framework to deliver a shared future. Planning grant, 2009, 2008-2009, 2013 (Box 126, Folder 14)
        File number N 28/7/46
      - #18573. Supporting peace building and advocacy in North Belfast, 2010 (Box 126, Folder 15)
      - #18573. Supporting peace building and advocacy in north Belfast, 2005, 2008-2012 (Box 126, Folder 16-17)
        File number N 28/7/52
    - International Association for Community Development, 1999
      International Association for Community Development
      - Strategies for Democratic Renewal. International Association for Community Development Conference. Edinburgh, Scotland. 8th-12th April 1999, 1999 (Box 126, Folder 18)
    - International Fund for Ireland, 1994-2001
      International Fund for Ireland
      - Community Bridges Program, 1996-2001 (Box 126, Folder 19)
        File number N 18/13. No grant-related documents.
      - Material from Joe Kinds, IFI, 1994-1996 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Irish American Partnership, 1991-1995, 1997
      Irish American Partnership
      - #7131 (#92-29). H.E.L.P. (Higher Education Liaison Program), 1989, 1992-1995 (Box 127, Folder 2-3)
      - #7146 (#92-53). Belfast-Dublin economic corridor feasibility study, 1992-1995 (Box 127, Folder 4)
        International Economics/Trade
      - #7176 (#93-10). Townsend enterprise park, 1991-1995 (Box 127, Folder 5)
        Job Creation and Workforce Development
        Small Businesses
      - #7187. Travel expenses. Youth orchestra, 1993 (Box 168, Folder 11)
        Dublin office cabinet file 29/5
        Arts Exchange
        Arts Education
      - #7502 (#97-29). Travel stipend. Ulster Sports and Recreation Trust, 1997 (Box 127, Folder 6)
        Cycling
    - Irish Peace Institute, 1994-1998
      Irish Peace Institute
      - (#94-49). Conference on communication between northern and southern parts of island of Ireland (CANCELED), 1994-1995 (Box 127, Folder 8)
      - #7338 (#95-47). Core support. Research center: funding for Institute's secretary, 1995 (Box 127, Folder 9)
      - #7372 (#96-02). Staff support, 1995-1996 (Box 127, Folder 10)
      - #7372 (#96-02). Staff support, 1995-1998 (Box 127, Folder 11)
        File number N 17/6
    - Irish School of Ecumenics, 1998, 2000-2005
      Irish School of Ecumenics
      - #9310. Partners in Transformation, 1998, 2000-2005 (Box 127, Folder 12-13)
        File number N 17/26/1
    - Joseph Rowntree Charitable Trust, 1995-2004
      Joseph Rowntree Charitable Trust
      - Rowntree, 1995-1998, 2002-2003 (Box 127, Folder 14)
        File number N 18/4. No grant-related documents.
      - JRCT - endowment consultancy, 1997-2001, 2004 (Box 127, Folder 15)
        File number N 18/4/1. No grant-related documents.
      - #8430. Drumcree mediation, 2000-2003 (Box 127, Folder 16)
    - Juniper Consulting, 2010-2012
      Juniper Consulting
      - #17425. Enduring capacity to protect rights, 2010-2012 (Box 127, Folder 17)
        File number N 28/7/57
      - #18591. From Principles to Practice: cohesion, sharing, and integration in practice, 2010-2011 (Box 127, Folder 18)
        File number N 28/7/58
    - Kairos, 1999-2003
      Kairos
      - #7792 (#99-1). Project development consultant, 1999-2000 (Box 127, Folder 19)
      - #9204. Respite renewal center, 2001-2003 (Box 127, Folder 20)
        File number N 17/17/3.
    - Law Center NI, 2002, 2004-2014; Law Centre (NI)
      Law Centre (NI)
      - #13671. Planning grant, 2004-2005 (Box 127, Folder 21)
      - #13671. Planning grant, 2002, 2004-2005, 2008-2009 (Box 127, Folder 22-23)
        File number N 28/7/8
      - #13671. Supplemental materials, 2008-2010 (Box 127, Folder 24)
      - #14245. Policy Development Unit and Mental Health Initiative, 2005-2010, 2012 (Box 128, Folder 1-2)
        File number N 28/7/8/1.
        Patients' Rights
      - #20183. Law Center renewal, 2010-2013 (Box 128, Folder 3-4)
        File number N 28/7/59
      - #22664. Protect rights and increase access to justice and services. Final grant, 2010, 2014 (Box 128, Folder 5)
        File number N 28/7/82
    - Lifestart Foundation Ltd., 1998-1999, 2001-2012
      Lifestart Foundation Ltd.
      - Annual financial statements for year ended 31 March 2006, 2006 (Box 128, Folder 6)
      - Annual General Meeting, 2005/2006. Annual report, 2006 (Box 128, Folder 7)
      - Evaluations, 2004, 2006 (Box 128, Folder 8)
      - Lifestart Foundation. Strategy document, June 2007, 2007-06 (Box 128, Folder 9)
      - Lifestart Mid-ARDS, annual reports, 2002-2006 (Box 128, Folder 10)
      - Lifestart, 11/9 A, 2001-2003, 2006 (Box 128, Folder 11-12)
      - Report submitted to the Atlantic Philanthropies on the longitudinal evaluation and strengthening core competencies, 2008 (Box 128, Folder 13)
        File number N 27/8/27. No grant-related documents.
      - Report submitted to the Atlantic Philanthropies on the longitudinal evaluation and strengthening core competencies, 2009 (Box 128, Folder 14)
      - #11938. Evaluation of the Lifestart program. File 1, 1998-1999, 2002-2004, 2007 (Box 128, Folder 15-16)
        File number N 27/8/1
      - #11938. Evaluation of the Lifestart program. File 2, 2003-2008, 2010 (Box 128, Folder 17-18)
      - #15320. Evaluation of the Lifestart program. File 1, 2007-2009 (Box 128, Folder 19-20)
      - #15320. Evaluation of the Lifestart program. File 2, 2008-2010 (Box 128, Folder 21)
      - #18978. Evaluation continuation, 2009-2012 (Box 129, Folder 1-2)
    - Linen Hall Library, 1994-2004; Linen Hall Library (Belfast, Northern Ireland)
      Linen Hall Library (Belfast, Northern Ireland)
      Public Libraries
      - #7285 (#94-57) and #7418 (#96-43). Library expansion, 1957, 1994-1998, 2001-2003 (Box 129, Folder 3-4)
        File number N 21/2
      - #7539 (#97-66). Staff support. Core costs, 1997, 2004 (Box 129, Folder 5)
      - #7669 (#98-36). Renovation. Library extension, 1998-2001 (Box 129, Folder 6)
        Special Libraries
      - #9307. Consolidation program, 2001-2003 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Local Initiative for Needy Communities, 1995-2003; LINC Resource Centre (Belfast, Northern Ireland)
      LINC Resource Centre (Belfast, Northern Ireland)
      - Reports, 1998 (Box 129, Folder 8)
        File number N 17/4/1. No grant-related documents.
      - #7417 (#96-42). Core support. 1997-1998 (File 1), 1996-2002 (Box 129, Folder 9)
        File number N 17/4
      - #7417 (#96-42). Core support. File 2. 1995-1996, 1995-1996, 2001 (Box 129, Folder 10-11)
      - #7417 (#96-42). Core support. #7666 (#98-33). Salary support. #8026 (#00-49). Core support. #7842 (#99-51). Staff support. #8371. Conflict transformation program, 1998-2003 (Box 129, Folder 12)
        Welfare
      - #7666 (#98-33). Salary support. Conflict Transformation Project, 1997-2000 (Box 129, Folder 13)
        File number N 17/4/1
      - #7666 (#98-33). Salary support. Conflict Transformation Project - supplemental materials, 1996, 1999-2000, 2003 (Box 129, Folder 14-15)
      - #7842 (#99-51). Support worker, 1999-2001 (Box 129, Folder 16)
        File number N 17/4/2
      - #8026 (#00-49). Core support. Admin., 2000 (Box 129, Folder 17)
        File number N 17/4/4
      - #8371. Conflict Transformation Program. LINC II, 2000-2003 (Box 129, Folder 18-19)
        File number N 17/4/3
        - Floppy disks 1 and 2, FD-939--940 (Box 129, Folder 19)
          Floppy disks
    - London School of Economics and Political Science, 2008-2010
      - #16621. Human rights futures (LSE) (Francesca Klug), 2008-2010 (Box 129, Folder 20)
        File number N 28/7/32
    - Mayfair Business Centre Limited, 1999-2003, 2007; Mayfair Business Center Limited
      Mayfair Business Center Limited
      Business Promotion
      Information and Communications
      - Business Plan, October 1999, 1999-10 (Box 130, Folder 1)
      - #9320. Development project, 1996, 2000-2003, 2007 (Box 130, Folder 2-4)
        File number N 17/50
        - TARA. Â Mayfair Business Centre Ltd., FD-941 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Middlequarter Limited, 2010-2013
      Middlequarter Limited
      Palliative Care
      - #23354. Palliative care planning grant. GOAL fund, 2010-2013 (Box 130, Folder 5-7)
    - National Children's Bureau, 2002-2004, 2008-2014; NCB (NI)
      NCB (NI)
      - #16989. Building capacity to improve outcomes for children, 2002, 2004, 2009 (Box 130, Folder 8)
        File number N 27/9/7
      - #16989. Building capacity to improve outcomes for children. File 1, 2003, 2008-2011 (Box 130, Folder 9-10)
        File number N27/8/41
      - #16989. Building capacity to improve outcomes for children. File 2, 2009, 2011-2013 (Box 130, Folder 11)
        - The Connected Baby: a Film Conversation by Dr. Suzanne Zeedyk and Jonathan Robertson, 2011; DVD-3461 (Box 130, Folder 11)
      - #20092. NCB- Building capacity in children and youth participation, 2011-2014 (Box 130, Folder 12)
        File number N27/8/60
      - #21198. Improving children's services. File 1, 2012 (Box 130, Folder 13)
        File number N 27/8/66
      - #21198. Improving children's services. File 2, 2012-2013 (Box 130, Folder 14-15)
      - #21198. Improving children's services. File 3, 2013-2014 (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - National Development Team for Inclusion, 2009-2010; National Development Team for Inclusion (Great Britain)
      National Development Team for Inclusion (Great Britain)
      - #16043. CAP (Changing Ageing Partnership) evaluation, 2008-2010 (Box 131, Folder 1-2)
        File number N 26/8/11/2
        Changing Ageing Partnership
    - NEA Northern Ireland, 2007-2011
      NEA Northern Ireland
      Utility Expense Assistance
      - #16979. Warm Homes Campaign. File 1, 2007-2010 (Box 131, Folder 3-4)
        File number N 26/8/40
      - #16979. Warm Homes Campaign. File 2, 2009-2011 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - NI Assembly Legislative Strengthening Trust, 2009-2012, 2014
      NI Assembly Legislative Strengthening Trust
      - #19534. Building political leadership capacity at the Northern Ireland Assembly, 2009-2012, 2014 (Box 131, Folder 6-7)
        File number N 0/0/12
      - #22694. PoliticsPlus, 2014 (Box 131, Folder 8)
        File number N 0/0/16
    - N.I. Association for the Care and Resettlement of Offenders (NIACRO), 1995-2003, 2007; NIACRO (Organization)
      NIACRO (Organization)
      - General, 1999-2002 (Box 131, Folder 9)
      - Evaluation program, 1999-2000 (Box 131, Folder 10)
      - NIACRO - loose materials, 1996-1997, 1999, 2001 (Box 131, Folder 11-12)
        File number N 17/3. Primarily reports. No grant-related documents.
      - NIACRO - Old file > 1996., 1995-1996 (Box 131, Folder 13)
        File number N 17/3. No grant-related documents.
      - NIACRO - research, 1995-1996 (Box 131, Folder 14)
        File number N 17/3/1. No grant-related documents.
      - NIACRO - loose materials, 1997 (Box 131, Folder 15)
      - NIACRO Research (teach), 1998-1999 (Box 131, Folder 16)
        File number N 17/3/2. No grant-related documents.
      - Peacebuilding, 1998-1999, 2003, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 17)
        File number N 17/3/4. No grant-related documents.
      - #7381 (#96-11) and #7443 (#96-68). Research project support, 1996-1998 (Box 131, Folder 18-19)
        File number N 17/3/1
      - #7481 (#97-9). Model crime prevention program, 1996-1998, 2000 (Box 132, Folder 1-2)
        File number N 17/3.
      - #7481 (#97-9). Model crime prevention programs, 1997-1998 (Box 168, Folder 12)
        Dublin cabinet file Cab. 6, Dr. 3B 17/10/1/2
      - #7699 (#98-68). Program implementation. Restorative justice, 1997-2000, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 3-5)
      - #8045 (#00-68). Program support/planning support, 2000-2002 (Box 132, Folder 6-7)
      - #8242. Alternatives program, 1999-2000 (Box 132, Folder 8)
      - #8279. Truth finding process. Truth and reconciliation study, 1999-2002, 2007 (Box 132, Folder 9)
        File number N 17/28
      - #9492. Healing through Remembering, 2001-2003 (Box 132, Folder 10)
      - #10712. Healing through Remembering planning, 2002-2003, 2007 (Box 132, Folder 11)
    - NI Human Rights Consortium, 2010-2013
      NI Human Rights Consortium
      - #21228. Human Rights Consortium, 2010-2013 (Box 132, Folder 12-13)
        File number N 28/7/69
    - North Belfast Community Development Centre, 1986, 1990, 1997, 1999-2002; Community Development Centre (Belfast, Northern Ireland)
      Community Development Centre (Belfast, Northern Ireland)
      - #7819 (#99-28). Core support, 1986, 1990, 1997, 1999-2002 (Box 132, Folder 14-15)
      - #8717. Support to Mount Vernon Community Association and Lower Oldpark Community Foundation. Weak infrastructure, 1999-2002 (Box 132, Folder 16)
        File number N 19/10/1.
    - North Belfast Partnership, 1998-2000, 2002-2006
      North Belfast Partnership
      - North Belfast Partnership Board, 1998-2000 (Box 132, Folder 17)
        File number N 19/7. No grant-related documents.
      - Statements of need, 2003 (Box 132, Folder 18)
        File number N 19/7/1. No grant-related documents.
      - Urban II project, 2000, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 19)
      - #10624. Regranting to community development groups, 2002-2006 (Box 132, Folder 20)
        File number N 19/7/2
        Housing Development
      - #12073. Community group support, 2004, 2006 (Box 132, Folder 21)
        File number N 19/7/2/1
        Urban Renewal
    - North Eastern Education and Library Board, 2009-2013; Northern Ireland. North Eastern Education and Library Board
      Northern Ireland. North Eastern Education and Library Board
      - #17585. Shared Education Project (area based), 2009-2012 (Box 133, Folder 1-2)
        File number N 28/7/44
      - #20870. Shared education, 2011-2013 (Box 133, Folder 3)
        File number N 28/7/66
    - Northern Ireland Alternatives, 2002-2005, 2007, 2009-2010, 2014
      Northern Ireland Alternatives
      - #11552. Community based restorative justice. 'Eliminating punishment violence', 2002-2005, 2007, 2009-2010 (Box 133, Folder 4-5)
        File number N 23/7.
      - #15918. Supporting community based restorative justice. Pilot of community based mediation, 2007-2010 (Box 133, Folder 6-7)
        File number N 28/7/27
      - #24614. Restorative practice, 2014 (Box 133, Folder 8)
        File number N 28/7/84
    - Northern Ireland Council for Ethnic Minorities, 2003, 2005-2013
      Northern Ireland Council for Ethnic Minorities
      - #15586. Strengthening capacity planning grant, 2008 (Box 133, Folder 9)
      - #15586. Planning grant, 2003, 2005-2008 (Box 133, Folder 10)
        File number N 28/7/31
      - #16514. Lobbying, advocacy, and campaigning project, 2008-2012 (Box 133, Folder 11-12)
        File number N 28/7/38
      - #21078. Protecting rights and improving policy and services for minority ethnic communities in Northern Ireland, 1999, 2006-2008, 2011-2013 (Box 133, Folder 13-15)
        File number N 28/7/68
    - Northern Ireland Council for Integrated Education, 1990-1999
      Northern Ireland Council for Integrated Education
      - Capital fund, 1997-1999 (Box 133, Folder 16)
        File number N 13/2/1/3. No grant-related documents.
      - #7079 (#91-65). Integrated Education conference, 1991-1992 (Box 133, Folder 17)
      - #7147 (#92-54). Core support. Nursery education, 1992, 1995, 1997-1998 (Box 133, Folder 18)
      - #7147 (#92-54). Core support. Nursery education, 1992-1996, 1990, 1992-1996 (Box 133, Folder 19)
        File number N 13/2
    - Northern Ireland Council for Voluntary Action (NIVCA), 1992-2014; Northern Ireland Council for Voluntary Action
      Northern Ireland Council for Voluntary Action
      - Annual reports, plans, and reviews, 2006 (Box 134, Folder 1)
        No grant-related documents. Includes annual reports, development plan, operational plan with quarterly reviews and accounts.
      - Plans, accounts, and appendices, 2005-2006 (Box 134, Folder 2)
        No grant-related documents. Includes continuation of quarterly reviews/accounts, appendices, and management accounts.
      - Reports, 1997, 2002-2004 (Box 134, Folder 3-6)
        No grant-related documents. Includes various plans, reports, surveys, and analyses for NICVA Research Unit.
      - Reports and assessments, 1999-2001 (Box 134, Folder 7)
      - NICVA- CINNI, 1997 (Box 134, Folder 8)
        File number N 18/6/1.
      - NICVA - general, 1998-2002 (Box 134, Folder 9)
        File number N 18/6/3
        - NICVA. Annual report and accounts, CD-5285 (Box 134, Folder 9)
        - NICVA. Forging Links: annual report 2001-2002, 2002; CD-5286 (Box 134, Folder 9)
        - NICVA. Noble Deprivation Indicators Lookup Database, 2001; CD-5287 (Box 134, Folder 9)
      - NICVA - management training, 2001-2003 (Box 134, Folder 10)
        File number N 18/6/7
      - #7178 (#93-12). Citizen's Enquiry, 1992-1994 (Box 134, Folder 11)
      - #7363 (#95-74). Research project for policing Northern Ireland, 1996-1997 (Box 134, Folder 12)
      - #7444 (#96-69). Millennium review, 1996-12-19 (Box 134, Folder 13)
      - #7444 (#96-69). Millennium debate, 1996-2000 (Box 134, Folder 14-15)
        File number N 18/6
      - #7444 (#96-69). Millennium debate. Supplemental materials, 1996 (Box 134, Folder 16)
      - #7641 (#98-10). Johns Hopkins Comparative Non-Profit Sector Research Project. NICVA - research, 1995, 1997-2000 (Box 134, Folder 17)
        File number N 18/6/2
        Johns Hopkins University
      - #7952 (#99-157). Regional Community Resource Centre. File 1, 1999-2000 (Box 134, Folder 18)
        File number N 18/6/4
        Media Access and Policy
      - #7952 (#99-157). HQ and Community Resource Centre. File 2, 1998-2000 (Box 134, Folder 19-20)
      - #8039 (#00-62). Policy and Research Unit, 1999-2004 (Box 134, Folder 21)
        File number N 18/6/5
      - #8039 (#00-62). Policy and Research Unit. Research Advisory Group, 2002-06 (Box 134, Folder 22)
      - #8039 (#00-62). Policy and Research Unit. Membership survey, 2006-06 (Box 134, Folder 23)
      - #8039 (#00-62). Policy and Research Unit. Reports and studies, 2002-2005 (Box 135, Folder 1)
      - #8039 (#00-62). Policy and Research Unit. Survey Research Series Policy Papers, 2001-2003 (Box 135, Folder 2)
      - #8039 (#00-62). Policy and Research Unit. Scoping papers, 2001-2002 (Box 135, Folder 3)
      - #8039 (#00-62). Policy and Research Unit. Responses, 2001-2002 (Box 135, Folder 4)
      - #9245. IT proposals, 2001-2006, 2009 (Box 135, Folder 5)
        File number N 18/6/6
        Libraries
        Information Communications Technology
      - #11553. European and Public Policy unit, 2002-2005, 2007 (Box 135, Folder 6-7)
        File number N 18/6/9
      - #11554. Management Development program, 2003-2005, 2007 (Box 135, Folder 8-9)
        File number N 18/6/8
      - #11823. Support for core costs, 2004-2008 (Box 135, Folder 10-12)
        File number N 18/6/10
      - #13600. Joint Benefits Take Up Initiative, 2005-2006 (Box 135, Folder 13)
        Dublin audit file
      - #13600. Joint Benefits Take Up Initiative, 2004-2007 (Box 135, Folder 14)
        File number N 26/8/13
      - #13600. Benefit Take Up Initiative. Reporting period September 2005 to December 2005. Appendices, 2006-02 (Box 135, Folder 15)
      - #13600. Benefit Take Up Initiative. Reporting period September 2005 to December 2006, and appendices 4-7, 2006-2007 (Box 135, Folder 16)
      - #14911. Extension to BTUI feasibility period, 2006-2007 (Box 136, Folder 1)
        Access restrictions reply.
      - #14911. BTUI extension, 2006 (Box 136, Folder 2-3)
        File number N 26/8/13/1
      - #19430. Re-grants to support enduring capacity, 2008-2012 (Box 136, Folder 4-6)
      - #19430. To enable NICVA to make a series of re-grants that will support the enduring capacity of the age sector, 2010 (Box 136, Folder 7)